# Kolawole Odenusi

Mbabane, Hhohho Region, Eswatini

kayodenusi@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/kolawoleodenusi

## **Summary**

As a customer service representative, I have provided premium customer service to clients across the nation and around the world. My customers are my biggest focus while providing unparalleled customer service to ensure that my clients' experience is exceptional. I am committed to providing stellar customer service or excellence in all areas of the company, from directly servicing my clients, to making sure that order processing and admin are running smoothly. I pride myself on being thorough and caring for all of our clients' needs. I am also available to lead in the future as an instructor or trainer at their request.

As a customer service representative, my goal is to provide the best service possible to each and every client. I will strive to always exceed expectations and provide excellent customer service, which is why we are able to remain top-notch in our field.

## **Experience**

## **Customer Service Manager**

Green Cross Pharmacy International Online

Sep 2022 - Present (3 months +)

Promoted to Customer Support Team Manager and began handling further HR-based roles and coordinating further processes and deals with shippers.

## **Customer Service Representative**

Green Cross Pharmacy International Online

May 2020 - Sep 2022 (2 years 5 months)

Providing daily online customer support for orders and pharmaceutical products.

Processing and handling customer order data and payments.

Liaison with shippers and supply chain coordinators for customer packages and tracking.

## **Auditing Intern and Filing Clerk**

Joseph Botti & Associates

Jan 2018 - Nov 2019 (1 year 11 months)

Performed basic auditing tasks as an intern and kept track of all incoming files and documents for the firm.

#### Shelving Clerk

Pick n Pay

Nov 2017 - Dec 2017 (2 months)

Kept stock of various items in-store and interacted with and assisted customers, daily.

## **Education**

Assam Don Bosco University, Guwahati

Bachelor's of Computer Applications - BCA, Computer Applications Oct 2020 - Oct 2023

## **Licenses & Certifications**

- Diploma in Customer Relationship Management in Business Services Alison Empower Yourself
  1477-16539149
- **Diploma in Customer Service Revised 2017** Alison Empower Yourself 1238-16539149
- Certificate in Customer Service Skills Alison Empower Yourself 1929-16539149
- Diploma in Human Resources (HR) Management Alison Empower Yourself 1678-16539149

## **Skills**

Product Sourcing • Order Tracking • Employee Training • Customer Service Management • Internal Communications • Internal Audits • Quota Achievement • Talent Scouting • Customer Onboarding • People Management